Contacts

+79377673007 (Mobile)

vladislav.smirnov.work@yandex.ru

www.linkedin.com/in/vladislavsmirnov-914048154 (LinkedIn) beamish-cvv.netlify.app/ (Personal)

Vladislav Smirnov

Frontend React Developer

General

Hello:) I am a positive and independent Frontend React developer with commercial experience - 6 years, a year and a half in web development.

Resume site:

https://beamish-cvv.netlify.app/

My github and codewars:

https://github.com/dolsev?tab=repositories

https://www.codewars.com/users/dolsev

Tech stack so far by experience:

JavaScript/typescript - 8/10

CSS/SASS, HTML - 8/10

React, react-router-home - 7/10

Webpack - 8/10

Git - 9/10

Photoshop, Figma - 7/10

Node.js - 7/10

Redux - 6/10

SQL/no SQL - 6/10

Thanks to my fluency in English, I communicated with clients about projects directly, which significantly increased speed of

Thanks to my experience as senior in tax, I led projects personally without customer's follow-ups and worked in team in chain of manager - me - staff . I usually offer ideas for reducing some feautures site s for a faster release of the project.

I also communicate well with Google and OpenAI, which, when working, allows me to down the time of senior colleagues.

IT always been my field since the installation of Windows for my friends was familiar to me at the age of 12, and now I really love my sphere of work)

https://t.me/reactivdev

I play the guitar, I play football on streets and at home on gamepad)

Work Experience

IP Platonov, FW Games Frontend Developer oct 2022 - Present Moscow City, Russia

FW Games is an indie game development company. Currently developing MMOTD for audience 12+.

What I did on the project:

- completely rewrote the project under React;
- optimized the code for further development by adding styled-components;
- Participated in design and implementation
- supplemented the design at the request of the customer with a visual from Midjourney
- made a proofreading of the text in English, corrected the wording Project stack: React, JavaScript, styled-components, Webpack, Midjourney

IP-Platonov - e-commerce site selling piece furniture

What I did on the project:

- pixel-perfect layout of the design project from Figma
- connected data display via API, added sorting and filters
- wrote a shopping cart and the logic of working with the back on Redux

Project stack: React, JavaScript, sass, Webpack

EY

Frontend Developer feb 2022 - sep 2022 Moscow City, Russia Development of React components in English for the application to collect personal client information through forms

Participation in designing of the front-end of the application for clients Coordination between the IT department and the business department regarding application development

Cross-browser and responsive layout based on mockups Code review

Senior Consultant Tax feb 2018 - aug 2022 Russia

Education

Moscow State University Bachelor's degree, Law ·